One son, if you take the first politician,
you will be left out, you will get hundred percent
claim in insurance, I say
that you are thinking very wrong,
you will not get it, it is of utmost importance that if
you get insurance done, then
you will get hundred percent insurance
claim, there are many tractors due to which
we do
not get hundred percent interest rate, so
which are the parts and how can you get
your insurance claim off track,
so stay entered in the roots, so the
first thing you need from your department
because every phone call comes in this program, then the
insurance claim is found closed, his peepal
tree is found closed, you get hundred percent claim directly,
okay, so which are the tractors
due to which you are not getting
hundred percent, which parts are there, I will
come there, hello friends, my name is
but I will take it and today I have
brought a very good video for you, so you will do Bindas
Quest together, the first
point is Manju, when your insurance
claim seems to be rejected, the first reason is that
your  If you have a valid license then you do
n't have insurance. It's a simple matter. If you do
n't have a license and you are driving, then
you forget that you will get insurance. The
second thing that happens is that while driving, you forget that insurance. It is
directly
linked together. You will get an offer.
You will have to pay the entire amount from your pocket to bring your car. So
always keep these things in mind. If you
have this that you have subscribed to an end-cause plan, then
you will not get insurance. It will be
rejected. The second point is if your
car meets with an accident, then in that case,
you will have to
call, send a message, email, whatever you want to do.
Every company has a different
time. Some companies follow
24 hours and 50 hours. So
within this time, you have to inform the insurance company
that my car has met with an accident and is
parked here. You should check it for the last time. Or
whatever the matter is, the second and the whole thing is that now, in case of an accident,
one of your vehicles has met with an accident.  You should inform the
insurance company immediately
and then they will throw it in
front of the insurance company but friend the insurance company is
not that crazy, it understands that this sequence is dead, so
many times people develop this method,
it is heard that
in a week the children tell me some different way, I
call it an impact express, we do
not get to know that story immediately, many times it happens that
what is your car front, that is, the front
bumper, if you want a discount, then it has got a lot of birthday,
but it is available from the real side and
how did the rabbit come, then you are not able to fit your stories sarcastically, you are
not able to express your story so much in front of that inspector farmer who does the infrastructure, that it becomes clear to him
that your body in front is
tired, ghee in the back, then in that case you do
not get hundred percent insurance claim, it is
not your fault, someone will ask you, but
whenever you do not get hundred percent insurance claim in that case, the
fourth point is
many times when I have related this to this
water that your insurance is
being done, your car side is only, it has
tipped from the front to the rear, okay  But you are
not able to express your story with money in
front of the inspector, in front of the Infosys company,
Sudhir, that is a lot of trouble, you
don't get appointed as a national guardian, that is the reason,
suppose you went in front, read the message,
he hit you from behind because of a car coming from behind, then
how will you tell it, then you should put it there and tell your
story as fake, then the monastery goes up and down, so this is what happens,
how do you express your story, it is strange, then
we will get great tips
and if Bhrigu is not fitting, then you will
not get it, still this means small, you had a
real accident, recently you had an
accident, so whatever is reprinted somewhere in your back hidden
time, here is the
content, this is by inviting, then they
try to do that too, madam, this is
my Mitthu, this is also, this is also fine, if
we tow it to Africa, then it is fine, you will
get the amount of that too, and the story will be of that new
factory, and along with that, if
your car is admitted, then
show the last fifty percent of that, then
in such a market, you will say a lot, then when the old
Accident is also added to this,
in that case also your insurance claim gets rejected. What happens is
that you fill the capacity of your vehicle, for example, the
limit of the vehicle is 1200 kilowatts but
you are running 1500 kilowatts in it,
in that case also your insurance
claim can get rejected, so once you
check what is your capacity,
what is the limit of the vehicle, it is 1200 thousand, so
according to that, keep your vehicle
in the same condition as much as the car needs, if it gets damaged under
this condition then your
insurance claim can get rejected,
after this a good
interesting point was put to the innocent people
that when my vehicle accelerates, then
in that case we get the opposite stop and
excitement, that is why we get depression, now
what happens is that the vehicle gets damaged by lakhs of
reactors, then
you do
not get insurance claim for the damage that occurs due to this, now you
get the blouse which is the stock part of the vehicle  Such a
happy insurance claim is written here,
it is written in the policy, yes,
if you want, you can tell the company about the amount of your exercise
which you put in your Nagpur, that
we will put
pink or brown red chilli, one thing
medicines in it, now
whatever problem you have in the testicles, make this tree
modern according to that, you will get its special talent, you will get
hundred percent softness, it is
soft, it fights a lot,
Agra point, if your car is Accent, then it is
written in that case, which is the
geographical area, every company has
different areas,
something is written in the policy of some company, something is written in the policy of some company, then it is
written in their policy that you are
Accent on your side, it happens every day within India, then
you will get less, but if you
go outside and you have an accident, that is,
when you go to Bhutan and Nepal, then
you will not get credit there,
yes madam, I would like to do it,
why did I gather  Your insurance
claims get rejected in this also,
when people have a car accident,
many people do
not inform the insurance company
that my car has met with an accident
and they drive some inch loss prevent vehicles,
which means that the damage gets
increased and increases,
after that when we ask for the next one, it gets
rejected, so what is the big deal brother,
you have made a small problem big,
okay, where it was supposed to cost thousands of rupees,
now it is costing 10,000, that's all,
insurance companies will
respect it, so now include it in this,
whenever you have an accident,
quickly inform your Ghat insurance company within 12 hours, 24 hours, say within this hour,
you tell them that
my car has met with an accident and is
lying here, the car has come, can you check it, it is
in no condition at all, let's go,
whatever I am telling you, you
can increase it and you will get the full interpretation of the insurance claim,
absolutely true  Yes, you have
not to make any mistake, you are not
hiding anything, do not cause any infection and
you are taking care of the factors that I have told you,
what happens many times is that
you will have to make your story, it will increase, okay,
express Sahani in this way,
friend, bring Simran, she has to be fit, you are right and the
system will develop, it is very important, so that was all
for today, I like you all the
time, that is why your insurance claim gets
rejected, so from here today's
video is yours, thank you, you have so many pimples, I have
a small request, please subscribe to the channel
and do not forget to share,
thank you so much.